[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many arms does the octopus have?", "correct_answer": "8", "incorrect_answers": ["14", "12", "10"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does Sleeping Beauty usually do in the Shrek movies?", "correct_answer": "sleeps", "incorrect_answers": ["knits a sock", "spins", "eats apples"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What movie about side show performers, released in 1932, was banned from the UK for 30 years?", "correct_answer": "Freaks", "incorrect_answers": ["Metropolis", "Phantom of the Opera", "Scarface"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The African kingdom of Dahomey was powerful in the XVIII century. Which modern day country did it cover?", "correct_answer": "Benin", "incorrect_answers": ["Burma", "Burkina Faso", "DR Congo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The first sales of the Coca Cola drink were made at Jacobs Pharmacy in Atlanta, Georgia, in what year?", "correct_answer": "1886", "incorrect_answers": ["1798", "1900", "1800"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the mortality rate of a cheetah cub growing to adulthood?", "correct_answer": "95% die", "incorrect_answers": ["50% die", "15% die", "65% die"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What 1958 movie starring John Agar tells the story of a mad scientist who made a machine to shrink people?", "correct_answer": "Attack of the Puppet People", "incorrect_answers": ["Planet of the Vampires", "The Shrinking Gun", "Land of the Giants"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Have sharks been around for about 400 million years?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Wii is a game console released by Nintendo.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the pigment that determines the color of human skin?", "correct_answer": "Melanin", "incorrect_answers": ["Melamine", "Antocian", "Melatonin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The groundbreaking design of this building was created by Danish architect, Jorn Utzon. It is located by the sea, and its roof resembles white sails.", "correct_answer": "Sydney Opera House", "incorrect_answers": ["Metropolitan Opera", "Carnegie Hall", "La Scala"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the very unusual dish Balut, popular in Vietnam, consist of?", "correct_answer": "Fertilized egg", "incorrect_answers": ["Rat meat", "Pigs brain", "Fish heads"]}]